

For over 5 years, I have been developing applications both as personal projects and professionally. I am experienced in both mobile and web development and have knowledge and experience in the entirety of the development cycle, from project start to deployment.

#### Github

github.com/gustavolemesleitebarbosa

#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/gustavo-lemes-207822132

### Webpage

gustavo-lemes-dev-portifolio.netlify.app

#### **Phone**

+55 19 98339-0686

#### **Email**

gustavolemesleite@gmail.com

## Work experience

# Software engineer

Profusion, Apr 20121 - Nov 2022

During my time at Profusion, I worked as software engineer on a big sports application targeted towards the American and European markets. My responsibilities included implementing interfaces, streaming features, and real-time updates using websockets. In addition to this, I also worked on other applications that incorporated features like IoT, hardware integration, and integrations with Google Analytics, REST, and Graphql APIs. My role also involved developing complex interfaces

## Software engineer

Griaule Biometrics, Aug 2020 - Mar 2021

At Griaule Biometrics, I worked as a software developer, focusing on the development of the company's biometric suite. My main areas of responsibility were the fingerprint detection and fingerprint extraction tools, which I helped to develop from scratch.

## Software engineer

OneBrain, Fev 2019 - Apr 2020

During my time at Onebrain, I had the opportunity to work on diverse and exciting projects across different industries, such as automotive, food, and retail. One of the most challenging projects was a disruptive venture focused on complex audio processing. As a mobile software engineer, I collaborated closely with a team of talented developers and engineers to deliver innovative solutions.

#### Intern

Affinity Petcare, Jun 2015 – Jun 2016

As an intern at Affinity Pet Care, I had the opportunity to participate in a job rotation program that provided me with a comprehensive understanding of the company's operations. Throughout the rotation, I worked alongside experienced professionals in different departments.

## **Education & Learning**

### Rocketseat Mobile BootCamp

rocketseat.com.br, Feb 2023

### Rocketseat Fullstack BootCamp

rocketseat.com.br, Aug 2020

### Master of Science in Mechanical Engineering

UNICAMP (State University of Campinas) graduated 2019

### Academic Interchange

Czech Technical University
5 monhs in interchange end at Mar 2014

### **Bachelor in Mechatronics Engineering**

UNICAMP (State University of Campinas), graduated 2016

#### Skills

Experienced with: React. ReactQuery, Redux,
Tailwind-Css, Styled-components, Sass, NextJs,
GraphQL, T3stack, React native, Xamarin, Android
(both with views and Jetpack compose), HTML,
CSS, Git, Github, NodeJs, Prisma ORM, TypeORM,
Typescript, Javascript, Java, Kotlin, Sanity
headless CMS, Vercel, Netlify.

## Languages

